Here's to the crazy ones.
敬那些瘋狂的人。
The misfits. The rebels.
格格不入的人。反叛的人。
The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes.
惹麻煩的人。方孔裡的圓釘。
The ones who see things differently.
看事情跟別人不一樣的人。
They're not fond of rules, and they have no respect for the status quo.
他們不喜歡規矩，也不尊重現狀。
You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them.
你可以引用他們、反對他們、歌頌或詆毀他們。
About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things.
唯一不能做的，是忽視他們——因為他們改變事情。
They push the human race forward.
他們推動人類向前。
And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see…
有人看見瘋子，我們看見——
…genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world,
——天才。因為瘋狂到以為自己可以改變世界的人，
are the ones who do.
才是真正改變了世界的人。